Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - N
        - Nebula - Nebula 1, 1988; SR-22761; Nebula (Box 369)
        - Nebula Nine - Keep it coming, 1996; SR-22762; Nebula Nine (Box 370)
          Catalog # Clubhead 001; A-side Matrix # ClubHead 001-A
          Clubhead Records
          Cincinnati, Ohio
        - Neecy Dee - Best of me, 1985; SR-22763; Neecy Dee (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22764. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # PAL 7067 DJ; A-side Matrix # PAL 7067 A
          TNT Records
        - Neecy Dee - Best of me, 1984; SR-22764; Neecy Dee (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22763. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # TN-1226; A-side Matrix # TNT 1226 A
        - Neeva - Will you be mine, 1982; SR-22765; Neeva (Box 370)
          Catalog # DNC 12-2; A-side Matrix # DNC-12-2-A
          Mutiny Shadow International
        - Nefatini - Don't stop, 1990; SR-22766; Nefatini (Box 370)
          Catalog # FMS 62375; A-side Matrix # FMS-62375-1
          Select Records
        - Nefertiti - Visions of Nefertiti, 1994; SR-22767; Nefertiti (Box 370)
          Catalog # PRO 1118-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1118-1
        - Nefertiti - Visions of Nefertiti, 1994; SR-22768; Nefertiti (Box 370)
        - Nefertiti - Miss Amutha Nature, 1993; SR-22769; Nefertiti (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22770. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # 862 871-1; A-side Matrix # 422-862-871-1A
        - Nefertiti - Miss Amutha Nature, 1993; SR-22770; Nefertiti (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22769. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nefertiti - Visions Of Nefertiti, 1994; SR-22771; Nefertiti (Box 370)
          Catalog # PRO 1098-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1092-1
        - Nefertiti - Visions Of Nefertiti, 1994; SR-22772; Nefertiti (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22773. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nefertiti - Visions Of Nefertiti, 1994; SR-22773; Nefertiti (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22772. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nefertiti - Visions Of Nefertiti, 1994; SR-22774; Nefertiti (Box 370)
        - Negro Jetro - Matador | Reggae reggae, 1994; SR-22775; Negro Jetro; Los Intocables (Box 370)
          Catalog # MM 101 A; A-side Matrix # MM-101-AA
          Marlon Music
        - Negrocan - Cada vez, 2000; SR-22776; Negrocan; Lord G; Nelson, Grant (Box 370)
          Catalog # RM0178; A-side Matrix # RM-0178A
          Rampage
        - Neighborhood Crew - Face to face (with the music), 1986; SR-22777; Neighborhood Crew (Box 370)
          Catalog # FR001; A-side Matrix # FR-001A
          Neighborhood Crew
        - Neighborhoods - …The high hard one..., 1986; SR-22778; Neighborhoods (Box 370)
          Catalog # 72112-1; A-side Matrix # 72112-1-A S-1559
          Restless Records
          El Segundo, California
        - Nelly - Errtime, 2005; SR-22779; Nelly; Jung Tru; King Jacob (Box 370)
          Catalog # UNIR 21424-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-21424-1A
          Universal Records
        - Nelly - E.I., 2000; SR-22780; Nelly (Box 370)
          Catalog # UNIR-20101-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20101-1A
        - Nelly - Ride wit me, 2001; SR-22781; Nelly; City Spud (Box 370)
          Catalog # UNIR 20399-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20399-1A
        - Nelly - Flap your wings; My place, 2004; SR-22782; Nelly; Jaheim (Box 370)
          Catalog # B0003154-11; A-side Matrix # B0003154-11A
        - Nelly - Batter up, 2000; SR-22783; Nelly (Box 370)
          Promo. It says the date is 2001 on discogs, but the record itself says 2000
          Catalog # UNIR 20379-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20379-1A
        - Nelly - Batter up, 2000; SR-22784; Nelly (Box 370)
          Promo. It says the date is 2001 on discogs, but the record itself says 2001
        - Nelly - Batter up, 2000; SR-22785; Nelly (Box 370)
          Promo. It says the date is 2001 on discogs, but the record itself says 2002
        - Nelly - E.I., 2000; SR-22786; Nelly (Box 370)
        - Nelly - Errtime, 2005; SR-22787; Nelly; Jung Tru; King Jacob (Box 370)
        - Nelly - Country grammar (hot....), 1999; SR-22788; Nelly (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22789. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # U8P 1672; A-side Matrix # U8P-1672-1A
        - Nelly - Country grammar (hot....), 1999; SR-22789; Nelly (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22788. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nelly - Tilt ya head back, 2004; SR-22790; Nelly; Aguilera, Christina (Box 370)
          Catalog # UNIR 21325-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-21325-1A
        - Nelson - Love you forever, 1988; SR-22791; Nelson; Nelson, Robert; Lord Nelson (Box 370)
          Catalog # JR 005; A-side Matrix # JR-005A
          Joker Records
        - Nelson - Gimme Something, 1986; SR-22792; Nelson; Nelson, Robert; Lord Nelson (Box 370)
          Catalog # NCR 384; A-side Matrix # NCR-384-RE1-A
          Charlie's Records
        - Nelson - Hotter than hot, 1984; SR-22793; Nelson; Nelson, Robert; Lord Nelson (Box 370)
          Catalog # BSR-NEL-006; A-side Matrix # BSR-NEL-006-A
          B's Records
        - Nelson, Andy - Lady Angie, 1982; SR-22794; Nelson, Andy (Box 370)
          Catalog # 8214; A-side Matrix # 8214A
          Carrere
          Paris, France
        - Nelson, Sandy - Beat that #?!* drum, 1966; SR-22795; Nelson, Sandy (Box 370)
          Catalog # LP-12329; A-side Matrix # LP 12329
          Imperial
          Los Angeles, California
        - Nelson, Shara - Down that road, 1994; SR-22796; Nelson, Shara (Box 370)
          Catalog # Y-58036; A-side Matrix # Y-58036-A-RE3
          Chrysalis
        - Nelson, Shara - Down that road, 1994; SR-22797; Nelson, Shara (Box 370)
        - Nelson, Shara - U, 1999; SR-22798; Nelson, Shara; Kasha (Box 370)
          Catalog # BOS2024; A-side Matrix # BOS-2024-A2
          Botchit & Scarper
        - Nelson, Tyka - L.O.V.E., 1988; SR-22799; Nelson, Tyka (Box 370)
          Catalog # 4V9 43293; A-side Matrix # 4V9 43293 A
        - Nemesis - Drop tha bottom, 1995; SR-22800; Nemesis (Box 370)
          Catalog # PRO-7431-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7431-0-A-RE1
        - Nemesis - Cantfiguritout; Get ya flow on, 1993; SR-22801; Nemesis (Box 370)
          Catalog # PRO-7407-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7407-A
        - Nemesis - Temple of boom, 1993; SR-22802; Nemesis (Box 370)
          Catalog # PRO-1441-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1441-A
        - Neon - Skydiver, 1981; SR-22803; Neon (Box 370)
          Catalog # FUDS 8103; A-side Matrix # FUDS-8103-A
          Fuschia International
        - Neosoul - For the chosen few, 1999; SR-22804; Neosoul (Box 370)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # OT-008; A-side Matrix # OT-008-A
          Orbit Transmission Records
          Costa Mesa, California
        - Neosoul - Introfusion EP, 1998; SR-22805; Neosoul (Box 370)
          Catalog # OT-006; A-side Matrix # OT-006-A
        - Neotropic - 15 levels of magnification, 1997; SR-22806; Neotropic (Box 370)
          Catalog # NTONE 21; A-side Matrix # NTONE 21 A1
          Ntone
        - N*E*R*D - Lapdance, 2001; SR-22807; N*E*R*D; Harvey, Lee; Vita (Box 370)
          Catalog # VUST 196; A-side Matrix # 8387641 1A1 VUST 196
          Virgin
        - N*E*R*D - Provider, 2003; SR-22808; N*E*R*D (Box 370)
          Catalog # 7243 5 46915 6 0; A-side Matrix # 546 9156 A-1-1
        - N*E*R*D - Maybe (remixes), 2004; SR-22809; N*E*R*D (Box 370)
          Catalog # 7087 6 18592 1 8; A-side Matrix # 7087-6-18592-1A
        - N*E*R*D - She wants to move, 2004; SR-22810; N*E*R*D (Box 370)
          Catalog # 7087 6 18545 1 0; A-side Matrix # 7087-6-18545-1-0-A-REI
        - Nervus Sistem - Just fa dolo, 1995; SR-22811; Nervus Sistem (Box 370)
          Catalog # BFL00001; A-side Matrix # BFL-1-A
          BFL Records
          New Jersey
        - Nervus Sistem - Just fa dolo, 1995; SR-22812; Nervus Sistem (Box 370)
        - Nesby, Ann - Lovin' is really my game, 2000; SR-22813; Nesby, Ann; Thunderpuss; Hurley, Steve "Silk" (Box 370)
          Catalog # AMRR-10158-1; A-side Matrix # AMRR-10158-1-A
          Perspective Records
          North Hollywood, California
        - Ness - About me (disc one), 2002; SR-22814; Ness (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22815; SR-22816. Double album.
          Catalog # 017 943-1; A-side Matrix # DF102-4 0179421 A
          Universal Licensing Music
        - Ness - About me (disc two), 2002; SR-22815; Ness (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22814; SR-22816. Double album.
          Catalog # 017 943-1; A-side Matrix # DF102-4 0179421 C
        - Ness - Heart beat, 2002; SR-22816; Ness (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22814; SR-22815. Different discs.
          Catalog # 015711 1; A-side Matrix # 0384 1015 711-1 A
        - Loz Netto's Bzar - Loz Netto's Bzar, 1983; SR-22817; Loz Netto's Bzar (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22818. Different discs.
          Catalog # 210.003; A-side Matrix # 210 003-A
          21 Records
          Netherlands
        - Loz Netto's Bzar - Loz Netto's Bzar, 1982; SR-22818; Loz Netto's Bzar (Box 370)
          In same jacket as # SR-22817. Different discs.
          Catalog # 2311 187; A-side Matrix # 198 2311187 1 380
        - Netzwerk Florida - Earth.Wind.Fire/, 2002; SR-13927; Netzwerk Florida (Box 371)
          Catalog # MON 002; A-side Matrix # MON-002-A
          Monotone
          Palm Beach, Florida
        - Netzwerk Florida - Earth.Wind.Fire/, 2002; SR-22819; Netzwerk Florida (Box 371)
        - N.E.U.K. - Wartime | Run they gonna kill yall, 1997; SR-22820; N.E.U.K.; Infared; Dilly, John (Box 371)
          Catalog # PE37; A-side Matrix # PE-37-A
          Paradox Entertainment
        - Nevels Sisters - Now is the time to seek the lord, 1990; SR-22821; Nevels Sisters (Box 371)
          Catalog # 1001; A-side Matrix # 0X105A
          Versa Records
          Toledo, Ohio
        - Nevil, Robbie - C'est la vie, 1985; SR-22822; Nevil, Robbie (Box 371)
          Catalog # V-56036; A-side Matrix # V-1 56036 X241139 B-A
          Manhattan Records
        - Nevil, Robbie - Just like you, 1991; SR-22823; Nevil, Robbie (Box 371)
          Catalog # SPRO 4772; A-side Matrix # SPRO-04772-Z2
        - Nevil, Robbie - Somebody like you, 1989; SR-22824; Nevil, Robbie (Box 371)
          Catalog # V-56125; A-side Matrix # V-1-56125-Z1-DMM
        - Nevil, Robbie - C'est la vie, 1986; SR-22825; Nevil, Robbie (Box 371)
        - Neville Brothers - Sister Rosa, 1989; SR-22826; Neville Brothers (Box 371)
          Catalog # SP-12306; A-side Matrix # SP-012306-A ES1
        - Neville Brothers - Neville-ization (live at Tipitina's New Orleans, Louisana), 1984; SR-22827; Neville Brothers (Box 371)
          Catalog # BT-1031; A-side Matrix # BT-1031-A
          Black Top Records
          New Orleans, Louisiana
        - New Birth - Kute girls, 1982; SR-22828; New Birth (Box 371)
          Catalog # JT-13301; A-side Matrix # PD 13301-A
          RCA
        - New Birth - Golden classics, 1988; SR-22829; New Birth (Box 371)
          Catalog # DPL1-0860; A-side Matrix # DPL1-0860 A-1
          Collectables
          Narberth, Pennsylvania
        - New Birth - Blind baby, 1975; SR-22830; New Birth (Box 371)
          Catalog # BDS 5636; A-side Matrix # BDS 5636-A
          Buddah Records
        - New Child - Get paid shorty, 1997; SR-22831; New Child (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA8P 4088; A-side Matrix # MCA 13047
          MCA Records
        - New Choice - People want bass, 1988; SR-22832; New Choice (Box 371)
          Catalog # 0-21166; A-side Matrix # 0-21166-A
          Warner Bros. Records
        - New Choice - At last, 1988; SR-22833; New Choice (Box 371)
          Catalog # 1-25752; A-side Matrix # 1-25752-A-RE1-SH1
        - New Direction - Golden horizon, 1990; SR-22834; New Direction; Ebanks, Rudy (Box 371)
          Catalog # G.B.I. 223-90; A-side Matrix # 223-90-A-1
          G.B.I. Recording Studios
          Freeport, Bahamas
        - New Edition - Mr. Telephone Man, 1984; SR-22835; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # L33-1259; A-side Matrix # MCA-4300-FDS-1
        - New Edition - Once in a lifetime groove, 1986; SR-22836; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # L33-17212; A-side Matrix # MCA-6221-FW-1
        - New Edition - Candy girl, 1983; SR-22837; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # SWRL 3301; A-side Matrix # SWRL 3301A
        - New Edition - If it isn't love, 1988; SR-22838; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA-23830; A-side Matrix # MCA-7516-361
        - New Edition - Candy girl, 1982; SR-22839; New Edition (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22840. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # SWRL-2208; A-side Matrix # SWRL-2208-A
        - New Edition - Candy girl, 1982; SR-22840; New Edition (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22839. 2 copies.Promo
        - New Edition - N.E. heart break, 1989; SR-22841; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA-23891; A-side Matrix # MCA-8176-FDS-1
        - New Edition - Under the blue moon, 1986; SR-22842; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA-5912; A-side Matrix # MCA-6257-PL1
        - New Edition - Hit me off, 1996; SR-22843; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA8P-3776; A-side Matrix # MCA12604 BG1
        - New Edition - With you all the way, 1986; SR-22844; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA-23650; A-side Matrix # MCA-5596-FDS-2
        - New Edition - Hit me off, 1996; SR-22845; New Edition (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22846. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # MCA8P-3792; A-side Matrix # MCA-12614-36
        - New Edition - Hit me off, 1996; SR-22846; New Edition (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22845. Different discs.
          Catalog # MCA12 55224; A-side Matrix # MCA-12628-BG1
        - New Edition - You're not my kind of girl, 1988; SR-22847; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # L33-17710; A-side Matrix # MCA-8423-FDS-1
        - New Edition - I'm still in love with you; You don't have to worry, 1996; SR-22848; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA 12-55278; A-side Matrix # MCA-12704
        - New Edition - You're not my kind of girl (extended version), 1988; SR-22849; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # MCA-23903; A-side Matrix # MCA-8282-FDS-1
        - New Edition - Once in a lifetime groove, 1986; SR-22850; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # L33-17212; A-side Matrix # MCA-6221-FW-5
        - New Edition - Once in a lifetime groove, 1986; SR-22851; New Edition (Box 371)
        - New Edition - You're not my kind of a girl, 1988; SR-22852; New Edition (Box 371)
          Catalog # L33-17655; A-side Matrix # MCA-8282-FDS-1
        - New Edition - Hit me off, 1996; SR-22853; New Edition (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22854. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # MCA8P 3789; A-side Matrix # MCA 12629-BG1
        - New Edition - Hit me off, 1996; SR-22854; New Edition (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22853. Different discs. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # MCA8P 3792; A-side Matrix # MCA 12614-361
        - New Horizons - Your thing is your thing, 1983; SR-22855; New Horizons (Box 371)
          Catalog # 44-03888; A-side Matrix # XSS-169305-1A
        - New Jersey Mass Choir - I want to know what love is, 1985; SR-22856; New Jersey Mass Choir (Box 371)
          Catalog # SCS 0004; A-side Matrix # SCS-0004-A
          Savoy Records, Inc.
          Elizabeth, New Jersey
        - New Guys On The Block - On the dance floor, 1983; SR-22857; New Guys On The Block (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22858. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # SH-456; A-side Matrix # VID-254-A-1
          Sugar Hill Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - New Guys On The Block - On the dance floor, 1983; SR-22858; New Guys On The Block (Box 371)
          In same jacket as # SR-22857. 2 copies.Promo
        - New Guys On The Block - The New Guys On The Block, 1984; SR-22859; New Guys On The Block (Box 371)
          Catalog # SH 9203; A-side Matrix # VID-337-A
        - NKOTB - Dirty dawg, 1993; SR-22860; NKOTB; New Kids On The Block (Box 371)
          Catalog # 44 77315; A-side Matrix # XSS-77315-A-1A
        - New Kids On The Block - You got it (the right stuff), 1988; SR-22861; New Kids On The Block (Box 371)
          Catalog # 44 08132; A-side Matrix # XSS-08132-A
        - New Kids On The Block - You got it (the right stuff), 1988; SR-22862; New Kids On The Block (Box 371)
        - New Kids On The Block - Please don't go girl, 1988; SR-22863; New Kids On The Block (Box 371)
          Catalog # 44 07569; A-side Matrix # XSS-177584-1B
        - New Kids On The Block - Stop it girl, 1986; SR-22864; New Kids On The Block (Box 371)
          Catalog # CAS 2486; A-side Matrix # XSS 173907-1A
        - New Kingdom - Cheap thrills (live version), 1994; SR-22865; New Kingdom (Box 371)
          Catalog # 162440596; A-side Matrix # 162-440 596-1 AS HS
          Gee Street
        - New Kingdom - Cheap thrills (live version), 1994; SR-22866; New Kingdom (Box 371)
        - New Latin Age - Mama, 1990; SR-22867; New Latin Age (Box 371)
          Catalog # FLY 027; A-side Matrix # FLY 027 A
          Flying Records
          Napoli, Italy
        - New Models - Sight and sound, 1983; SR-22868; New Models (Box 371)
          Catalog # PVC 5903; A-side Matrix # PVC-5903-A-RE
          PVC Records
          South Plainfield, New Jersey
        - New Order - Low-life, 1985; SR-22869; New Order (Box 371)
          Catalog # 1-25289; A-side Matrix # 1-25289-A-SR3
          Qwest Records
        - New Order - Blue Monday, 1983; SR-22870; New Order (Box 372)
          Catalog # FACTUS 10; A-side Matrix # FACTUS-10 A 15850 (3) +
          Factory (US)
          San Francisco, California
        - New Order - True faith (disc one), 2001; SR-22871; New Order (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22872. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-100663; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100645-A-SRI
        - New Order - True faith (disc two), 2001; SR-22872; New Order (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22871. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-100663; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100645-C-SRI
        - New Order - Movement, 1981; SR-22873; New Order (Box 372)
          Catalog # FACT. 50; A-side Matrix # FAC-50-US-A
        - New Order - The perfect kiss, 1985; SR-22874; New Order (Box 372)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2342; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2342-SH1 B-21579-SH1
        - New Paradise - Showman, 1979; SR-22875; New Paradise (Box 372)
          Catalog # FLP 253 L; A-side Matrix # SLP-253-A
          Laser Records
        - New Power Generation - The good life, 1995; SR-22876; New Power Generation (Box 372)
          Catalog # 9 43537-0; A-side Matrix # 0-43537-A-SR1
          NPG Records
        - New Power Generation - Come on, 1998; SR-22877; New Power Generation (Box 372)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # NPG COME ON-A WHAT A LIFE!
        - New World Poet - Agony, 1994; SR-22878; New World Poet (Box 372)
          Catalog # BTR455LP; A-side Matrix # BTR-455-A
          Black Tower Records
        - New World Poet - (Strive) on your side; Gimme mine, 1996; SR-22879; New World Poet (Box 372)
          Catalog # BTR457LP; A-side Matrix # BTR-457-A
        - New York City Band - New York City Band, 1979; SR-22880; New York City Band (Box 372)
          Catalog # AILP 3002 DJ; A-side Matrix # AILP-3002-AS
          American International Records
        - New York Citi Peech Boys - Life is something special, 1982; SR-22881; New York Citi Peech Boys; Peech Boys; N.Y.C. Peech Boys (Box 372)
          Catalog # DMD 393; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-43947-43948-6
          Island Records
        - N.Y.C. Peech Boys - Life is something special, 1982; SR-22882; N.Y.C. Peech Boys; Peech Boys; New York Citi Peech Boys (Box 372)
          Catalog # 90094-1; A-side Matrix # ST-1L 835291-C
        - N.Y.C. Peech Boys - Life is something special, 1982; SR-22883; N.Y.C. Peech Boys; Peech Boys; New York Citi Peech Boys (Box 372)
        - N.Y.C. Peech Boys - Life is something special, 1982; SR-22884; N.Y.C. Peech Boys; Peech Boys; New York Citi Peech Boys (Box 372)
        - New York Express - Hot on the clue; A-bomb calling, 1982; SR-22885; New York Express; Denton, Mickey (Box 372)
          Catalog # DMD 350; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-41902-1
          Cherie
        - New Yorkers - My baby knows (I like it), 1974; SR-22886; New Yorkers (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22887. Different discs.
          Catalog # CAD 001; A-side Matrix # CAD-001A
          Camille Records
        - New Yorkers - My baby knowes (I like it) [sic], 1974; SR-22887; New Yorkers (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22886. Different discs.Test Pressing
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # CAD-001A
        - Newberry, Booker - Take a piece of me, 1986; SR-22888; Newberry, Booker (Box 372)
          Catalog # DMD 929; A-side Matrix # ST DM 49368-49369-1
          Omni Records
        - NewCity Rockers - Black dog, 1987; SR-22889; NewCity Rockers (Box 372)
          Catalog # CR8528; A-side Matrix # CR-8528-AS
          Critique
          Reading, Massachusetts
        - Newcleus - Jam on it | Ex'tra T's boogie, 1992; SR-22890; Newcleus; Extra T's (Box 372)
          Catalog # HCL 2229; A-side Matrix # HCL-2229-A
          Sunnyview
          Miami, Florida
        - Newcleus - Jam on revenge (the wikki-wikki song), 1983; SR-22891; Newcleus (Box 372)
          Catalog # SUN 408; A-side Matrix # SUN 408-A-RE
        - Newkirk - I desire, 1989; SR-22892; Newkirk (Box 372)
          Catalog # 44 73109; A-side Matrix # XSS-73109-A-1A
        - Newton-John, Olivia - Twist of fate, 1983; SR-22893; Newton-John, Olivia (Box 372)
          Catalog # L33-1150; A-side Matrix # MCA-3728-PL4
        - Newton-John, Olivia - Greatest hits, 1982; SR-22894; Newton-John, Olivia (Box 372)
          Catalog # 1C 088-64 956; A-side Matrix # 64956-A2
          EMI Electrola GmbH
          Germany
        - Newversion - Let's do it in the dancehall, 1990; SR-22895; Newversion (Box 372)
          Catalog # SAM-5015; A-side Matrix # SAM-5015-A C1 G1
          Sam Records
          Elmhurst, New York
        - Next Diffusion - Dritto dal cuore (straight from da heart) (disc one), 1995; SR-22896; Next Diffusion; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22897. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # SQUAD 035 LP; A-side Matrix # SQUAD 035 LATO N TEST1
          Crime Squad
        - Next Diffusion - Dritto dal cuore (straight from da heart) (disc two), 1995; SR-22897; Next Diffusion; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22896. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # SQUAD 035 LP; A-side Matrix # SQUAD 035 LATO X TEST1
        - Next Level - Find a way, 1995; SR-22898; Next Level (Box 372)
          Catalog # CR-327; A-side Matrix # CR-327 A AATB
          Cutting Traxx
        - Next Movement - Let's work it out, 1982; SR-22899; Next Movement (Box 372)
          Catalog # PRL D 542; A-side Matrix # PRLD-542-A
          Prelude Records
        - Nameless & Faceless - Next train I'm out, 2001; SR-22900; Nameless & Faceless (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22901. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CC-LP-004; A-side Matrix # BAAC-001-A
          Creative Control Records
        - Nameless & Faceless - Next train I'm out, 2001; SR-22901; Nameless & Faceless (Box 372)
          In same jacket as # SR-22900. 2 copies.
        - Ngema, Mbongeni - Time to unite, 1988; SR-22902; Ngema, Mbongeni; Cast of "Sarafina!" (Box 372)
          Catalog # MLPS 9811; A-side Matrix # MLPS 9811 A 1-1
          Mango
        - Ngema, Mbongeni - Mbongeni Ngema's Sarafina!, 1988; SR-22903; Ngema, Mbongeni; Masekela, Hugh (Box 372)